A Guide to the Papers of Joseph Blotner, 1976
Special Collections Department, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Papers of Joseph Blotner, 1976
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
7258-o
This collection consists of 10 items.
Administrative Information
Access
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
This collection was a gift of Joseph Blotner through Albert Erskine of Random House, January 25, 1977.
Scope and Content Information
This collection consists of various copies of Selected Letters of William Faulkner, edited by Joseph Blotner. There is also a Faulkner family genealogical chart.
Contents List
- Selected Letters of William Faulkner, edited by Joseph Blotner 1976, TMs, 5 folders (Box 1)
  Publisher's setting copy, p. 1-635
- Selected Letters of William Faulkner, edited by Joseph Blotner 1976, TMs, 34 p., 2 folders (Box 2)
  Publisher's setting copy, p. 625-764 and Index
- Selected Letters of William Faulkner, edited by Joseph Blotner 1976, Galley proof, 200 l, 4 folders (Box 2)
  With publisher's corrections
- Selected Letters of William Faulkner, edited by Joseph Blotner 1976, Galley proof, 43 l. (Box 3)
- Selected Letters of William Faulkner, edited by Joseph Blotner 1976, Page proof, 234 l., 5 folders (Box 3)
- Selected Letters of William Faulkner, edited by Joseph Blotner 1976, Pages, 144 l., 10 loose pages (Box 4)
  With a few editor's corrections; folded and cut gatherings of blue line
- Selected Letters of William Faulkner, edited by Joseph Blotner 1976, Revised repros., 86 p. (Box 4)
  With corrections
- Selected Letters of William Faulkner, edited by Joseph Blotner 1976, Master set repros., 2 folders (Box 4)
  With a few corrections, p. 1-465
- Selected Letters of William Faulkner, edited by Joseph Blotner 1976, Master set repros., 2 folders (Box 4)
  p. 1-463 (2nd copy)
- Faulkner family genealogical chart for Selected Letters of William Faulkner n.d., Oversize